<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Agility</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.agility.com/en/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.agility.com/en</link>
	<description>A Logistics Leader</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 07:59:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.8</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.agility.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/cropped-Agility-ico2-1-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Agility</title>
	<link>https://www.agility.com/en</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Agility Malaysia Receives 30 Years of Excellence Award</title>
		<link>https://www.agility.com/en/2018/10/agility-malaysia-receives-30-years-of-excellence-award/</link>
		<comments>https://www.agility.com/en/2018/10/agility-malaysia-receives-30-years-of-excellence-award/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 04:43:44 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Manoj Arumugam]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.agility.com/?p=15724</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Recognizes achievements in events logistics KUALA LUMPUR, Malaysia – October 18, 2018 – Agility, a leading global logistics provider, received the 30 Years of Excellence Award from the Malaysian Association of Convention and Exhibition Organisers and Suppliers (MACEOS). The award...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en/2018/10/agility-malaysia-receives-30-years-of-excellence-award/">Agility Malaysia Receives 30 Years of Excellence Award</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en">Agility</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Recognizes achievements in events logistics</em></p>
<p><strong>KUALA LUMPUR, Malaysia – October 18, 2018</strong> – Agility, a leading global logistics provider, received the 30 Years of Excellence Award from the Malaysian Association of Convention and Exhibition Organisers and Suppliers (MACEOS).</p>
<p>The award honors Agility Malaysia for its outstanding achievements in the business events industry. In Malaysia, Agility is a recognized leader in full-service, end-to-end management of trade fairs, expositions and events transportation.  Agility has handled a number of major exhibitions in Malaysia, including key defense, sports and entertainment events, auctions and fine arts showcases.</p>
<p>The evaluation for the award was based on criteria that include at least 30 years of continuous success and commitment in achieving excellence, financial stability, and professional integrity,  as well as a commitment and contribution to the community in addition to industry and market leadership.</p>
<p>“Agility has come a long way to become a cohesive organization with employees who work toward mutual goals and contribute to business excellence. We are undergoing a digital transformation that will continue to enable us to innovate and improve the way we meet the logistics requirements of our customers and bring more convenience to the community,” Agility Malaysia CEO Richard Strollo said.</p>
<p>MACEOS is an association of roughly 100 companies, including exhibition organizers, conference organizers, destination management and event management companies, venue owners, hoteliers, IV/AV suppliers, stand contractors and freight forwarders. MACEOS is recognized as the voice of the meetings, incentives, conferences and events (MICE) industry in Malaysia, and has a focus on education to build human capacity for the industry.</p>
<p><strong>About Agility</strong></p>
<p>Agility Global Integrated Logistics is one of the world’s top freight forwarders and providers of contract logistics. It offers ocean, air and road freight, warehousing and distribution, and integrated supply chain services in more than 100 countries. Agility GIL also provides specialist solutions for capital projects, oil and gas, chemicals, and fairs and events logistics. GIL and its parent, Agility, are pioneers in emerging markets, and leader and investors in the use of technology to enhance supply chain efficiency.  Agility is a publicly traded company with $4.6 billion in annual revenue.</p>
<p>For more information about Agility, visit <a href="http://icm-tracking.meltwater.com/link.php?DynEngagement=true&amp;H=5eXH0qSKdBRphS6WO4YlQwwSTi8wtQOqejFjZKiddbCzZ5Bbl4XDYakdcLfw%2FHu8kkKlrj2O8n3XaDEXioNkOUOm8CvXmgM8J2UXDna4aFez68wBOOso93ioYP2BbwD%2B&amp;G=0&amp;R=www.agility.com&amp;I=20181018010001.000000484545%40mail6-43-usnbn1&amp;X=MHwxMDQ2NzU4OjViYzczODJjYmQ3OTdkYzNiZjc2YjRjNzs%3D&amp;S=uKmcXVTWbQ1KkqFclc-0-iDeNRnkenRqHSzRcS4UhBY">www.agility.com</a></p>
<p>Twitter: twitter.com/agility</p>
<p>LinkedIn: linkedin.com/company/agility</p>
<p>YouTube: youtube.com/user/agilitycorp</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en/2018/10/agility-malaysia-receives-30-years-of-excellence-award/">Agility Malaysia Receives 30 Years of Excellence Award</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en">Agility</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.agility.com/en/2018/10/agility-malaysia-receives-30-years-of-excellence-award/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Agility’s Carbon Measurement Tool Certified by the Carbon Trust</title>
		<link>https://www.agility.com/en/2018/10/agility-carbon-measurement-tool-certified-by-the-carbon-trust/</link>
		<comments>https://www.agility.com/en/2018/10/agility-carbon-measurement-tool-certified-by-the-carbon-trust/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 06:07:56 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Manoj Arumugam]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.agility.com/?p=15669</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Certification gives customers opportunity to accurately offset estimated CO2 emissions KUWAIT CITY – October 17, 2018 – The Carbon Trust, an independent expert in sustainable strategies and technologies, has validated the methodology and processes that Agility uses to generate carbon...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en/2018/10/agility-carbon-measurement-tool-certified-by-the-carbon-trust/">Agility’s Carbon Measurement Tool Certified by the Carbon Trust</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en">Agility</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Certification gives customers opportunity to accurately offset estimated CO2 emissions </em></p>
<p><strong>KUWAIT CITY – October 17, 2018 –</strong> The Carbon Trust, an independent expert in sustainable strategies and technologies, has validated the methodology and processes that Agility uses to generate carbon footprint reports for logistics customers.</p>
<p>The Carbon Trust’s assurance allows Agility to demonstrate that its carbon reporting methodology and processes comply with the organization’s reporting guidance for transparency and accuracy. To receive assurance, Agility developed a methodology to ensure the accurate monitoring, quantifying and reporting of CO2 emissions data from the movement of customer cargo.  This methodology was audited extensively and approved by the Carbon Trust, and it has now been incorporated into Agility’s carbon reporting processes.</p>
<p>Agility has been providing free carbon footprint reports to customers since 2009, enabling them to track and reduce the amount of CO2 emissions created in their supply chains. With the Carbon Trust assurance, Agility’s customers can now use the free CO2 reports to offset emissions resulting from the transportation of their shipments. This information is also available to small and medium-sized logistics customers (SMEs) using <a href="https://www.shipafreight.com/">Shipa Freight</a>, the online freight service powered by Agility. Shipa Freight customers will get free CO2 emissions estimates for their shipments when they receive quotes and invoices.</p>
<p>Frank Clary, Agility’s Vice President of Corporate Social Responsibility, said: “Agility and others in the logistics industry are determined to address the challenge of climate change. The Carbon reporting that is validated by an internationally recognized expert such as the Carbon Trust is a key part of this. Armed with accurate information, our customers can understand their carbon footprint and take steps to create cleaner, and in some cases zero-emission supply chains by offsetting reported CO2 emissions.”</p>
<p>Clary said that for the first time SMEs can also make use of carbon-estimating technology to scrutinize their supply chains and choose shipment options that reduce their emissions. “<a href="http://www.shipafreight.com">Shipa Freight</a>, our online freight platform, provides SME customers with this information even at the quote stage. That helps them make informed, accurate decisions for their business and the environment.”</p>
<p>Hugh Jones, Managing Director, the Carbon Trust, said: &#8220;Companies are starting to pay a lot of attention to the carbon emissions in their supply chains, especially in areas with the highest impacts such as logistics. By taking a best practice approach to emissions measurement, Agility is able to meet this demand by supplying its customers with accurate, credible data which they can rely on to understand, manage and offset carbon emissions. At the same time, Agility’s Carbon Trust-assured measurement should unlock new opportunities, demonstrating Agility&#8217;s competitive advantage in offering carbon cutting solutions, which are often synonymous with efficiency and effective cost savings.&#8221;</p>
<p>Agility uses sustainable business practices in its own operations and works with customers and suppliers to develop and adopt sustainable practices. EcoVadis, an independent organization that evaluates and rates corporate sustainability programs, recently ranked Agility in the top 4 percent in environmental performance in its industry.</p>
<p><strong>About Agility</strong></p>
<p>Agility is a global logistics company with $4.6 billion in annual revenue and 22,000+ employees in more than 100 countries. It is one of the world’s top freight forwarding and contract logistics providers, and a leader and investor in technology to enhance supply chain efficiency. Agility is a pioneer in emerging markets and one of the largest private owners and developers of warehousing and light industrial parks in the Middle East, Africa and Asia. Agility’s subsidiary companies offer fuel logistics, airport services, commercial real estate and facilities management, customs digitization, and remote infrastructure services.</p>
<p>For more information about Agility, visit <a href="http://www.agility.com">www.agility.com</a></p>
<p>Twitter: twitter.com/agility</p>
<p>LinkedIn: linkedin.com/company/agility</p>
<p>YouTube: youtube.com/user/agilitycorp</p>
<p><strong>For more information:<br />
</strong>Sabrina Mundy</p>
<p>teamagility@manbitesdog.com</p>
<p>+44 1273 716 826</p>
<p>Man Bites Dog</p>
<p><strong>About the Carbon Trust</strong></p>
<p>Established in 2001, the Carbon Trust works with businesses, governments and institutions around the world, helping them contribute to – and benefit from – a more sustainable future through carbon reduction, resource efficient strategies, and commercialising low carbon businesses, systems and technologies.</p>
<ul>
<li>We work with corporates and governments, helping them to align their strategies with climate science and meet the goals of the Paris Agreement.</li>
<li>We provide expert advice and assurance, giving investors and financial institutions the confidence that green finance will have genuinely green outcomes.</li>
<li>We provide independent insight and support the development low carbon technologies and solutions, building the foundations for the energy system of the future.</li>
</ul>
<p>Headquartered in London, we have a global team of over 30 nationalities based across five continents.</p>
<p><strong>For more information: </strong></p>
<p>press@carbontrust.com</p>
<p>+44(0)207 170 7050</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en/2018/10/agility-carbon-measurement-tool-certified-by-the-carbon-trust/">Agility’s Carbon Measurement Tool Certified by the Carbon Trust</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en">Agility</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.agility.com/en/2018/10/agility-carbon-measurement-tool-certified-by-the-carbon-trust/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Agility Appointed to Handle Futurebuild 2019 in London</title>
		<link>https://www.agility.com/en/2018/09/agility-appointed-to-handle-futurebuild-2019-in-london/</link>
		<comments>https://www.agility.com/en/2018/09/agility-appointed-to-handle-futurebuild-2019-in-london/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 09:06:26 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Manoj Arumugam]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.agility.com/?p=15179</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Official freight and on-site handler for leading “built environment” event LONDON – September 27, 2018 – Agility, a leading global logistics provider, has been appointed as the official freight and on-site handling contractor for Futurebuild 2019, the leading event for...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en/2018/09/agility-appointed-to-handle-futurebuild-2019-in-london/">Agility Appointed to Handle Futurebuild 2019 in London</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en">Agility</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Official freight and on-site handler for leading “built environment” event</em></p>
<p><strong>LONDON – September 27, 2018</strong> – Agility, a leading global logistics provider, has been appointed as the official freight and on-site handling contractor for Futurebuild 2019, the leading event for “built environment” industries that include construction, engineering, architecture, design, planning, materials, landscaping and sustainment.</p>
<p>Held annually at ExCeL London, Futurebuild showcases the latest built environment ideas and technology and is expected to draw more than 26,500 senior decision makers and other visitors.  Agility will provide full global exhibition freight and on site services including; freight forwarding; pre- and post-show warehouse handling; and forklift and heavy lift operations.</p>
<p>Martin Hurn, Managing Director of Futurebuild Events, said: “Agility has a proven track record of supporting the delivery of some of the world’s leading events and exhibitions, and its expertise will be a huge benefit to our exhibitors and visitors in making sure the event runs smoothly. As Agility is onsite at ExCeL, we’re able to significantly reduce road freight in the run up to Futurebuild 2019. This also means we can make use of vast storage space, and maximize re-use of exhibition materials in future events.”</p>
<p>Garcia Newell, Business Development Director for Agility Fairs &amp; Events UK, said: “Our extensive experience working at ExCeL London, as well as our onsite facilities, will help Agility provide seamless services to both Futurebuild Events and their exhibitors.”</p>
<p><strong>About Agility</strong></p>
<p>Agility is a global logistics company with $4.6 billion in annual revenue and 22,000+ employees in more than 100 countries. It is one of the world’s top freight forwarding and contract logistics providers, and a leader and investor in technology to enhance supply chain efficiency. Agility is a pioneer in emerging markets and one of the largest private owners and developers of warehousing and light industrial parks in the Middle East, Africa and Asia. Agility’s subsidiary companies offer fuel logistics, airport services, commercial real estate and facilities management, customs digitization, and remote infrastructure services.</p>
<p>For more information about Agility, visit <a href="http://icm-tracking.meltwater.com/link.php?DynEngagement=true&amp;H=btYXC68syxnIlVIaW0qBweEUHWPFwuN5EgnqFgPj0oiC1OMl9zi1RlRdXVwsYBdpk2CpUrgy0CS5jGMz5hlT29rScKEDM47bj%2B%2ByiugT6SvbtyVvqeon0V9cLoXmnzPM&amp;G=0&amp;R=www.agility.com&amp;I=20180927080003.00000012be4d%40mail6-113-ussnn1&amp;X=MHwxMDQ2NzU4OjViYWJhMjc1NDU1MjY2ZGY3ZmM0OGNlOTs%3D&amp;S=uKmcXVTWbQ1KkqFclc-0-iDeNRnkenRqHSzRcS4UhBY">www.agility.com</a></p>
<p>Twitter: twitter.com/agility</p>
<p>LinkedIn: linkedin.com/company/agility</p>
<p>YouTube: youtube.com/user/agilitycorp</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en/2018/09/agility-appointed-to-handle-futurebuild-2019-in-london/">Agility Appointed to Handle Futurebuild 2019 in London</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en">Agility</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.agility.com/en/2018/09/agility-appointed-to-handle-futurebuild-2019-in-london/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Agility&#8217;s statement as a clarification to what was in the news related to Amghara plot 1,2,3</title>
		<link>https://www.agility.com/en/2018/09/agilitys-statement-as-a-clarification-to-what-was-in-the-news-related-to-amghara-plot-123/</link>
		<comments>https://www.agility.com/en/2018/09/agilitys-statement-as-a-clarification-to-what-was-in-the-news-related-to-amghara-plot-123/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 12:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Manoj Arumugam]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Investor Relations]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.agility.com/?p=15167</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Dear Investor, Kindly find below what was disclosed on Boursa Kuwait today as a clarification on what was mentioned in Al- Qabas newspaper. “With reference to the above subject and to what was published in Al Qabas newspaper issue no.16275...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en/2018/09/agilitys-statement-as-a-clarification-to-what-was-in-the-news-related-to-amghara-plot-123/">Agility&#8217;s statement as a clarification to what was in the news related to Amghara plot 1,2,3</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en">Agility</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dear Investor,</p>
<p>Kindly find below what was disclosed on Boursa Kuwait today as a clarification on what was mentioned in Al- Qabas newspaper.</p>
<p>“With reference to the above subject and to what was published in Al Qabas newspaper issue no.16275 dated 23 September 2018 and pursuant to the company&#8217;s disclosure dated 4 July 2018, the company filed against the Public Authority of Industry “PAI” and others case No. 3587/2018 Commercial/Civil/Government/24 requesting a judgment confirming the renewal of  the contractual agreement between the company and the Public Authority of Industry and the continuation of the lease agreement dated 29/11/1989 No.157 for the first, second and third phase of “South Amghara Scrap” that resulted into case No. 3686/2018 Commercial/Civil/Government/24 requesting a judgment  to prevent the Public Authority of Industry from disturbance of the company’s possession, use, exploitation and its investments of the plots subject to the same lease agreement. And case No. 4522/2018 Commercial/Civil/Government/1 requesting the delegation of the Ministry of Justice experts to proceed with the conciliation evidenced by the final requests and the ruling to prove the renewal of the contractual agreements between the company and the Public Authority of Industry in continuation of the same lease agreement and to prevent disturbance by “PAI” and others.</p>
<p>The company asserts that it was not notified of the termination of the contract, or the evacuation of the site, or that there is an objection on its presence in any way before the end of the contractual period provided for in the contract, and that the eviction notice was only given on the date of 3/7/2018, i.e. after the contract entered into a renewal period without objection from “PAI”.  The necessary legal measures will be taken to challenge the decision of evacuation in front of the courts.”</p>
<p><strong>Sincerely,</strong></p>
<p><strong>Investor Relations Department</strong></p>
<p><strong>Agility Public Warehousing Company</strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en/2018/09/agilitys-statement-as-a-clarification-to-what-was-in-the-news-related-to-amghara-plot-123/">Agility&#8217;s statement as a clarification to what was in the news related to Amghara plot 1,2,3</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en">Agility</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.agility.com/en/2018/09/agilitys-statement-as-a-clarification-to-what-was-in-the-news-related-to-amghara-plot-123/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Agility Receives WDA(H) Authorisation for Pharmaceuticals</title>
		<link>https://www.agility.com/en/2018/09/agility-receives-wdah-authorisation-for-pharmaceuticals/</link>
		<comments>https://www.agility.com/en/2018/09/agility-receives-wdah-authorisation-for-pharmaceuticals/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 09:05:20 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Manoj Arumugam]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.agility.com/?p=15072</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Authorisation covers two pharmaceutical facilities in the United Kingdom BRISTOL, United Kingdom – September 17, 2018 – Agility, a leading global logistics provider, has received a Wholesaler Distribution Authorisation (for Medicines for Human Use) from the UK Medicines Healthcare &#38; Regulatory...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en/2018/09/agility-receives-wdah-authorisation-for-pharmaceuticals/">Agility Receives WDA(H) Authorisation for Pharmaceuticals</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en">Agility</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>Authorisation covers two pharmaceutical facilities in the United Kingdom</em></p>
<p><strong>BRISTOL, United Kingdom – September 17, 2018</strong> – Agility, a leading global logistics provider, has received a Wholesaler Distribution Authorisation (for Medicines for Human Use) from the UK Medicines Healthcare &amp; Regulatory Agency (MHRA).</p>
<p>The certification, referred to as WDA(H), authorizes warehousing and cross-dock of a wide range of pharmaceuticals, including finished products and active pharmaceutical ingredients (API) under ambient and cold chain conditions.</p>
<p>The certification covers the Agility-managed pharma storage facility at London’s Heathrow Airport and a second pharma competence centre in Bristol. The WDA(H) allows Agility  to provide a number of additional services, including pick-and-pack operations for the distribution of stored products to hospitals, pharmacies and other distributors, the re-packing into active and passive shipping configurations, and the distribution of clinical trial materials.</p>
<p>Colm McAlinden, Managing Director for Agility Area North West, said, “With this new certification, we are able to expand our Life Science service offerings in the UK and operate on behalf of our customers, particularly virtual wholesalers, brokers and importers. The certification also provides Agility with flexibility for post-Brexit import and export regulations.”</p>
<p>In the UK, Agility also provides logistics services to the aerospace, automotive, hi-tech, and retail industries. Agility offers more than 27,000 sqm of open and bonded warehouse space across 17 locations, including temperature-controlled storage. Agility’s combination of local service and global resources has helped it establish relationships spanning 15 to 20 years with many customers in the country.</p>
<p><strong>About Agility</strong></p>
<p>Agility brings efficiency to supply chains in some of the globe’s most challenging environments, offering unmatched personal service, a global footprint and customized capabilities in developed and developing economies alike. Agility is one of the world’s leading providers of integrated logistics. It is a publicly traded company with more than $4.6 billion in revenue and more than 22,000 employees in over 500 offices across 100 countries. Agility’s core commercial business, Global Integrated Logistics (GIL), provides supply chain solutions to meet traditional and complex customer needs. GIL offers air, ocean and road freight forwarding, warehousing, distribution, and specialized services in project logistics, fairs and events, and chemicals. Agility’s Infrastructure group of companies manages industrial real estate and offers logistics-related services, including e-government customs optimization and consulting, waste management and recycling, aviation and ground-handling services, support to governments and ministries of defense, remote infrastructure and life support.</p>
<p>For more information about Agility, visit <a href="http://www.agility.com/">agility.com</a></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Twitter:</strong><a href="https://twitter.com/agility"> twitter.com/agility</a></li>
<li><strong>LinkedIn:</strong><a href="http://linkedin.com/company/agility"> linkedin.com/company/agility</a></li>
<li><strong>YouTube:</strong><a href="http://youtube.com/user/agilitycorp"> youtube.com/user/agilitycorp</a></li>
</ul>
<p>Photo Caption: <em>From left to right: Agility team members, David Adlam (Regional Manager, Republic of Ireland &amp; South West UK), Paul Morris (Strategic Account Manager, Life Science Area North West), Eric Ten Kate (Vice President, Global Life Science) and Brendan Mansell (Heathrow Warehouse Manager) inaugurate the new WDA(H) authorised pharma storage facility at London’s Heathrow Airport.</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en/2018/09/agility-receives-wdah-authorisation-for-pharmaceuticals/">Agility Receives WDA(H) Authorisation for Pharmaceuticals</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en">Agility</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.agility.com/en/2018/09/agility-receives-wdah-authorisation-for-pharmaceuticals/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Agility Supports LOYAC! KON Social Entrepreneurship Program</title>
		<link>https://www.agility.com/en/2018/08/agility-supports-loyac-kon-social-entrepreneurship-program/</link>
		<comments>https://www.agility.com/en/2018/08/agility-supports-loyac-kon-social-entrepreneurship-program/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 11:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Manoj Arumugam]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.agility.com/?p=14396</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>KUWAIT CITY, Kuwait – 9 August 2018 – Agility, a leading global logistics provider, took part  in the mentorship and training of 55 students enrolled in this year’s LOYAC! KON Social Entrepreneurship Program, in collaboration with Babson College.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en/2018/08/agility-supports-loyac-kon-social-entrepreneurship-program/">Agility Supports LOYAC! KON Social Entrepreneurship Program</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en">Agility</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>KUWAIT CITY, Kuwait – 9 August 2018</strong> – Agility, a leading global logistics provider, took part  in the mentorship and training of 55 students enrolled in this year’s LOYAC! KON Social Entrepreneurship Program, in collaboration with Babson College.</p>
<p>Agility’s participation in the program comes as part of its continued sponsorship and support of LOYAC and KON. KON is a six-week program for middle school and high school students from across Kuwait. It encourages participants to transform their ideas into action and aims to develop responsible business solutions to our community’s most pressing challenges. By the end of the program, students will be able to present their business ideas before a jury panel and a Babson College professor.</p>
<p>On July 18, Agility’s volunteer mentors led by Lamia Hayat, Assistant Manager – Agility Ventures, and Abdullah Fakhra, Senior Manager – Agility Ventures, used a game to help the students understand the complex evolution of the supply chain industry.  The students learned how to develop a solid business structure and were told how the <a href="https://www.agility.com/en/agility-ventures/">Agility Ventures</a> team vets startups and what it looks for before investing in a company. The session also included a discussion on how technology is changing the logistics industry.</p>
<p>Following the presentation, Agility’s Warehouse Operations team, led by Tek Bahadur Karki, Director – Warehousing Operations, took the students on a tour of the 18,000 sqm warehouse facility. The team explained their day-to-day work and the integrated systems Agility has developed to keep track of the thousands of shipments and orders. The students also learned about the climate-controlled chillers used to store goods that must be kept frozen.</p>
<p>Agility and its Infrastructure companies are committed to support of talented youth by empowering them to achieve their goals. One of Agility’s Infrastructure companies, United Projects for Aviation Services Company (UPAC), a leading commercial real estate and facilities management company, is also sponsoring this year’s program.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.agility.com/en/agility-ventures/">Agility Ventures</a>, the corporate venture arm of Agility, partners with promising startups that are championing technologies that can help build faster and more secure and sustainable supply chains. Agility Ventures has invested in digital start-ups that bring new efficiency to e-commerce fulfillment and last-mile delivery for businesses and consumers.</p>
<p>LOYAC is a non-profit organization working towards the overall development of the youth. Its programs facilitate the professional development and personal growth of people ages six to 30. Babson College, located in Wellesley, Massachusetts in the United States, specializes in entrepreneurship education.</p>
<p>To find out more about Agility’s corporate social responsibility activities, please visit the company’s CSR page <a href="http://www.agility.com/EN/csr">www.agility.com/EN/csr</a>.</p>
<p><strong><u>About Agility</u></strong></p>
<p>Agility brings efficiency to supply chains in some of the globe’s most challenging environments, offering unmatched personal service, a global footprint and customized capabilities in developed and developing economies alike. Agility is one of the world’s leading providers of integrated logistics. It is a publicly traded company with more than $4.6 billion in revenue and more than 22,000 employees in over 500 offices across 100 countries.</p>
<p>Agility’s core commercial business, Global Integrated Logistics (GIL), provides supply chain solutions to meet traditional and complex customer needs. GIL offers air, ocean and road freight forwarding, warehousing, distribution, and specialized services in project logistics, fairs and events, and chemicals.</p>
<p>Agility’s Infrastructure group of companies manages industrial real estate and offers logistics-related services, including e-government customs optimization and consulting, waste management and recycling, aviation and ground-handling services, support to governments and ministries of defense, remote infrastructure and life support.</p>
<p>For more information about Agility, visit <a href="http://Agility.com">Agility.com</a><br />
Twitter: <a href="http://twitter.com/agility">twitter.com/agility</a><br />
LinkedIn: <a href="http://linkedin.com/company/agility">linkedin.com/company/agility</a><br />
YouTube: <a href="http://youtube.com/user/agilitycorp">youtube.com/user/agilitycorp</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en/2018/08/agility-supports-loyac-kon-social-entrepreneurship-program/">Agility Supports LOYAC! KON Social Entrepreneurship Program</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en">Agility</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.agility.com/en/2018/08/agility-supports-loyac-kon-social-entrepreneurship-program/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Agility’s Second Quarter 2018 Earnings Webcast</title>
		<link>https://www.agility.com/en/2018/08/agility-second-quarter-2018-earnings-webcast/</link>
		<comments>https://www.agility.com/en/2018/08/agility-second-quarter-2018-earnings-webcast/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 13:08:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Byron Mondala]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Investor Relations]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.agility.com/?p=14333</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Analyst/Investor Conference for the Second Quarter of 2018.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en/2018/08/agility-second-quarter-2018-earnings-webcast/">Agility’s Second Quarter 2018 Earnings Webcast</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en">Agility</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Analyst/Investor Conference for the Second Quarter of 2018</p>
<p>We wish to inform you that the Quarterly Analyst/Investor Conference was held through a Live Webcast at 2:00 pm local time on Thursday August 9th, 2018.</p>
<p>Please refer to this <a href="https://www.agility.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/Agility-Q2-2018-Earnings-Update-.pdf">document</a> for the minutes of the conference and the investor presentation (Q2-2018).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en/2018/08/agility-second-quarter-2018-earnings-webcast/">Agility’s Second Quarter 2018 Earnings Webcast</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en">Agility</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.agility.com/en/2018/08/agility-second-quarter-2018-earnings-webcast/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Agility Reports 19% Q2 Earnings Increase</title>
		<link>https://www.agility.com/en/2018/08/agility-reports-nineteen-percent-second-quarter-earnings-increase/</link>
		<comments>https://www.agility.com/en/2018/08/agility-reports-nineteen-percent-second-quarter-earnings-increase/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 12:43:18 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Manoj Arumugam]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Investor Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.agility.com/?p=14322</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>KUWAIT – August 6, 2018 – Agility, a leading global logistics provider, today reported second-quarter earnings of 13.8 fils per share on net profit of KD 20 million, an increase of 18.7% over the same period in 2017. Agility EBITDA grew 13.6% to KD 37.1 million. Revenue increased 12.3% to KD 384.2 million.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en/2018/08/agility-reports-nineteen-percent-second-quarter-earnings-increase/">Agility Reports 19% Q2 Earnings Increase</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en">Agility</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Agility Reports 19% Q2 Earnings Increase</strong></p>
<table width="572">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td width="90">&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</td>
<td width="89">Q2 2018</p>
<p>(Million KD)</td>
<td width="89">Q2 2017</p>
<p>(Million KD)</td>
<td width="69">Variance</p>
<p>(%)</td>
<td width="84">H1 2018</p>
<p>(Million KD)</td>
<td width="85">H1 2017</p>
<p>(Million KD)</td>
<td width="66">Variance</p>
<p>(%)</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="90">Revenue</td>
<td width="89">384.2</td>
<td width="89">342.1</td>
<td width="69">12.3%</td>
<td width="84">756</td>
<td width="85">662.6</td>
<td width="66">14.1%</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="90">Net Revenue</td>
<td width="89">124.3</td>
<td width="89">117.8</td>
<td width="69">5.5%</td>
<td width="84">248.9</td>
<td width="85">228.6</td>
<td width="66">8.9%</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="90">EBITDA</td>
<td width="89">37.1</td>
<td width="89">32.6</td>
<td width="69">13.6%</td>
<td width="84">74.8</td>
<td width="85">63.4</td>
<td width="66">18 %</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="90">Net Profit</td>
<td width="89">20</td>
<td width="89">16.8</td>
<td width="69">18.7%</td>
<td width="84">38.9</td>
<td width="85">31.4</td>
<td width="66">23.9%</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="90">EPS (fils)</td>
<td width="89">13.8</td>
<td width="89">11.6</td>
<td width="69">18.7%</td>
<td width="84">26.9</td>
<td width="85">21.7</td>
<td width="66">24%</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><strong>KUWAIT – August 6, 2018 </strong>– Agility, a leading global logistics provider, today reported second-quarter earnings of 13.8 fils per share on net profit of KD 20 million, an increase of 18.7% over the same period in 2017. Agility EBITDA grew 13.6% to KD 37.1 million. Revenue increased 12.3% to KD 384.2 million.</p>
<p>First-half earnings of 26.9 fils per share and net profit of KD 38.9 million were up 24%. First-half EBITDA was KD 74.8 million, an increase of 18%. Revenue for the first half was KD 756 million, an increase of 14.1%.</p>
<p>Tarek Sultan, Agility Vice Chairman and CEO, said: “Our second quarter results were in line with expectations and consistent with the previous growth trend the company has been seeing. Agility’s Infrastructure companies performed well, as did our logistics business, which witnessed another quarter of volume and revenue growth despite margin pressure.”</p>
<p><strong>Agility Global Integrated Logistics (GIL)</strong></p>
<p>Global Integrated Logistics (GIL) business strategy of effective trade lanes development, productivity optimization and defined tailor-made solutions to customers continued to generate favourable results. GIL gross revenue grew 13.4% to KD 289.3 million. Net revenue rose 5% to KD 66.7 million, primarily due to growth in Freight Forwarding and Contract Logistics. The respective revenue and net revenue growth rates for the first half were 14.5% to KD 567.4 million and 6.4% to KD 131.3 million.</p>
<p>Air freight continued its strong performance in Q2, driven by solid volume growth of 14% and stable yields compared to the same period of last year. Air freight net revenue grew 21.9% in Q2 and 20.3% in the first half. Ocean freight had consistent volume growth but with lower yields. In Q2, container volume increased 8.2% vs. Q2 2017. Ocean freight net revenue grew 7.4% in Q2 and 7.3% in the first half.</p>
<p>Regionally, Air freight and Ocean freight performance was strongest in the Americas, Asia Pacific and Europe.</p>
<p>Contract Logistics continued its steady growth, primarily in the Middle East and Asia Pacific, as a result of new business and effective utilization of facilities. Contract Logistics net revenue grew 3.2% in Q2 and 4.5% in the first half.</p>
<p>GIL&#8217;s net revenue margin was 23% in Q2, down from 24.9% a year earlier due to yield degradation in Road freight and Project Logistics, primarily in the Middle East and Europe. GIL’s EBITDA reached KD 9.3 million in Q2, and its EBITDA margin was 3.2%, slightly lower than 3.6% in Q2 2017. In the first half, EBITDA grew 13.3% to KD 16.8 million. EBITDA margin in the first half remained flat at 3% vs. the same period in the previous year.</p>
<p>GIL is accelerating its digital transformation to increase the efficiency of its business processes, gain business insights, develop innovative logistics solutions, differentiate its products and better connect to its customers,</p>
<p><strong>Agility’s Infrastructure Companies </strong></p>
<p>Agility’s Infrastructure group EBITDA rose 16.8% (after adjusting for the impact of the US government settlement in 2017), to KD 31.3 million in Q2. Revenue grew 9.5% to KD 97.5 million. For the first half of 2018, EBITDA grew by 20.1% and revenue by 14.8%. All entities in the group contributed to this performance.</p>
<p>Agility Industrial Real Estate continues to improve the efficiency of its operations in Kuwait. It also concluded its Phase I development in Riyadh of 80K sqm of warehousing capacity and started with Phase II, for which an additional 120K sqm will be delivered next year. Expansion in Africa is progressing according to plan as Agility Industrial Real Estate moves ahead with its development in Ghana and prepares to start new developments in Mozambique, Nigeria and Cote d’Ivoire.</p>
<p>Tristar, continues to expand its fuels operation with existing customers. Tristar is also investing and diversifying its operations by expanding in shipping and broadening its geographic reach.</p>
<p>National Aviation Services (NAS) operations in Kuwait are generally stable. NAS operations in Cote d’Ivoire and Afghanistan continue to be positive contributors to the group. In addition, NAS’s new operation in Uganda has contributed significantly in 2018. Operations in Tanzania and Morocco continue to bear down on our group, but Tanzania is poised for a turnaround in 2018 and has numerous opportunities in the pipeline.</p>
<p>GCS, a company specialized in digitizing customs, showed improved performance in the second quarter. GCS manages all customs’ activities at ports of Kuwait and aims to enhance customs modernization through its services.</p>
<p>UPAC revenue and profits increased during the second quarter. Operations at Kuwait Airport and other prominent locations in Kuwait continue to drive growth. In addition, construction of Reem Mall in Abu Dhabi is moving forward according to plan.</p>
<p><strong>Recap of Agility Q2 Financial Performance</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Agility’s net profit increased 18.7% to KD 20 million in Q2 2018. EPS was 13.8 fils vs.11.6 fils a year earlier.</li>
<li>Agility’s Q2 EBITDA increased 13.6% to KD 37.1 million.</li>
<li>Agility’s Q2 revenue rose 12.3%, to KD 384.2 million and net revenue increased by 5.5%.</li>
<li>GIL Q2 revenue grew by 13.4% to KD 289.3 million.</li>
<li>Infrastructure’s Q2 revenue grew 9.5% to KD 97.5 million.</li>
<li>Agility enjoys a healthy balance sheet with KD 1.7 billion in assets. Net debt position was KD 130.7 million as of June 30, 2018. Operating cash flow was KD 29.2 million for the first half of 2018.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong><u>About Agility</u></strong></p>
<p>Agility is one of the world’s leading providers of integrated logistics. It is a publicly traded company with more than $4.6 billion in revenue and more than 22,000 employees in over 500 offices across 100 countries. Agility Global Integrated Logistics (GIL) provides supply chain solutions to meet traditional and complex customer needs. GIL offers air, ocean and road freight forwarding, warehousing, distribution, and specialized services in project logistics, fairs and events, and chemicals. Agility’s Infrastructure group of companies manages industrial real estate and offers logistics-related services, including customs digitization, waste management and recycling, aviation and ground-handling services, support to governments and ministries of defense, remote infrastructure and life support.</p>
<p>For more information about Agility, visit Agility.com<br />
Twitter: twitter.com/agility<br />
LinkedIn: linkedin.com/company/agility<br />
YouTube: youtube.com/user/agilitycorp</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en/2018/08/agility-reports-nineteen-percent-second-quarter-earnings-increase/">Agility Reports 19% Q2 Earnings Increase</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en">Agility</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.agility.com/en/2018/08/agility-reports-nineteen-percent-second-quarter-earnings-increase/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Agility wins a contract from DLA</title>
		<link>https://www.agility.com/en/2018/07/agility-wins-a-contract-from-dla/</link>
		<comments>https://www.agility.com/en/2018/07/agility-wins-a-contract-from-dla/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 17:07:43 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Byron Mondala]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Investor Relations]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.agility.com/?p=14022</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Agility, through one of its subsidiaries, has been awarded a contract by the Defense Logistics Agency “DLA” to provide fuel storage services in Guam for a value of USD 62 million over 4 base years. The contract has a one...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en/2018/07/agility-wins-a-contract-from-dla/">Agility wins a contract from DLA</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en">Agility</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Agility, through one of its subsidiaries, has been awarded a contract by the Defense Logistics Agency “DLA” to provide fuel storage services in Guam for a value of USD 62 million over 4 base years. The contract has a one five year option period for a value of USD 82 million.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en/2018/07/agility-wins-a-contract-from-dla/">Agility wins a contract from DLA</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.agility.com/en">Agility</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://www.agility.com/en/2018/07/agility-wins-a-contract-from-dla/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
